Rayavaram Nagakalyani (1) Featured



Highly competent Professional with 2+ years of experience in Web Application Development using core .Net, C#, SQL Server, WebAPI and Basic Javascript, Basic Html, CI/CD pipelines and dev automations using Azure DevOps, Team City and Octopus



Total Experience: 2 Year(s) 2 Month(s) Current Designation: Software Engineer

Current Company: Intlfcstone Inida Pvt Limited Notice Period: 2 Months

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Highest Degree: None [None]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Hyderabad

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: C,C++,C#,GIT,ASP.Net MVC,WebAPI,Windows Services,SQL,Basics on HTML,basics on

Javascript, Rabbitmq, Azure, Teamcity, Octopus, Requirement Analysis, System Analysis, Interpersonal Skills, Communication

Skills, ASP. Net, OOPS, Data Structures

Verified: Email - id Phone Number |

Last Active: 17-Dec-20 Last Modified: 17-Dec-20

Summary

Highly competent Professional with 2+ years of experience in Web Application Development using core .Net, C#, SQL Server, WebAPI and Basic Javascript, Basic Html, CI/CD pipelines and dev automations using Azure DevOps, Team City and Octopus. A thorough professional with a proactive attitude, capable of thinking in and out of the box. Possess excellent interpersonal, communication and organizational skills.

Work Experience

Intifcstone Inida Pvt Limited as Software Engineer

Jun 2019 to Till Date

- Analyst and Programmer in designing and developing web interface for fund transfer and investigating payment failure using c#, Net MVC, Web API, Html, JavaScript, SQL.
- Support Engineer for existing application developed using c#, Net MVC, Web API, Html, JavaScript, SQL.
- Collaborated with testing team to iron out bugs and accommodate end user requirements.
- Understand and deliver projects using Agile and SDLC process
- Experience in functional and technical requirement analysis
- Collaborated with offshore team to deliver projects on time

DigitalDot Consultancy Private Lmited as Software Engineer

Jul 2018 to Jun 2019

- Analyst and Programmer in designing and developing web interface for investigating payment failure using c#, Net MVC, SQL.
- Support Engineer for existing application developed using c#, Net MVC, SQL
- Collaborated with testing team to iron out bugs and accommodate end user requirements.
- Understand and deliver user stories in scrum-based projects
- organize public speaking sessions for team

DigitalDot Consultancy Private Limited as Intern

Dec 2017 to Jul 2018

- Training on .Net and SQL technologies
- * Contributed for initial development of web interface to investigate payment failure using .net and SQL.
- * Training on providing support for existing application developed using c#,.Net
- * Training on interaction with clients and offshore teams to deliver projects on time

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics/Telecommunication) from VIT University in 2018

PG: None (None) in 0

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience	
C, C#,C++,SQL,.NetMVC, Windows services			2 Year(s) 2 Month(s)	
Jira, Git, Octopus, Teamcity, Trello			1 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	
Basics of Html, Basics of Javascript		0	1 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
WebAPI, RabbitMQ		0	0 Year(s) 6 Month(s)	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			

Affirmative Action

Category: General

Physically Challenged: No